James E. McDonald papers, (1904-1997)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup I: UFO Research Files, 1904-1971
  - Series 2: Project Blue Book, 1947-1968
    - February 16, 1961: 36.35 N. 67.45 W. Atlantic. (Box 17)
    - February 23, 1961: Misawa AB, Japan. (Box 17)
    - February 26, 1961: Tyndall AFB, Fla.. (Box 17)
    - February 27, 1961: Yuma, AZ. (Box 17)
    - February 27, 1961: Bark River, Mich.. (Box 17)
    - February 27, 1961: Herndon, VA. (Box 17)
    - February 28, 1961: Waverly AFB, Iowa. (Box 17)
    - March 3, 1961: Ephrata, Wash. (Box 17)
    - March 10, 1961: RAF Station, Upper Heyford, Eng. (Box 17)
    - March 13, 1961: Guard Island, AK. (Box 17)
    - March 23-29, 1961: Ft. Pierce, Fla. (Box 17)
    - April 11, 1961: Cape Canaveral, Fla. (Box 17)
    - April 14, 1961: Far East. (Box 17)
    - April 20, 1961: Hanna City AFS, IL. (Box 17)
    - May 11, 1961: Indian Springs, NV. (Box 17)
    - May 20, 1961: Maxwell AFB, Ala. (Box 17)
    - May 22, 1961: Tyndall AFB, Fla. (Box 17)
    - May 22, 1961: Maxwell AFB, Ala. (Box 17)
    - June 2, 1961: Tampa, Fla. (Box 17)
    - June 25, 1961: Pacific Ocean. (Box 17)
    - Spring !961: Kemah, TX. (Box 17)
    - July 7, 1961: Copemish, Mich. (Box 17)
    - July 10, 1961: Golden, Colo. (Box 17)
    - July 20, 1961: Houston, TX. (Box 17)
    - September 2, 1961: Albuquerque, NM. (Box 17)
    - September 7, 1961: Cape Canaveral, Fla. (Box 17)
    - September 27, 1961: Pacific Coast. (Box 17)
    - September 30, 1961: Las Vegas, Nev. (Box 17)
    - November 7, 1961: Arlington Heights, Ill. (Box 17)
    - November 21, 1961: Oldtown, Fla. (Box 17)
    - December 13, 1961: Washington DC. (Box 17)
    - January 22, 1962: Kirksville, Missouri. (Box 17)
    - February 12, 1962: Winnemucca AFB, Nevada. (Box 17)
    - March 26, 1952: Ramstein, Germany. (Box 17)
    - April 2, 1962: Goose Bay Labrador. (Box 17)
    - April 12, 1962: 220.2 N. 160.4 W. Kunia, Hawaii. (Box 17)
    - April 18, 1962: Nellis AFB Nevada. (Box 17)
    - May 19,1962: Marksville, Leesville, Colfax, LA. (Box 17)
    - May 24, 1962: Albuquerque, NM. (Box 17)
    - June 7, 1962: Hallett Station, Antarctica. (Box 17)
    - June 21, 1962: Indianapolis, Indiana. (Box 17)
    - August 18, 1962: Bermuda. (Box 17)
    - October 23, 1962: Farmington, Utah. (Box 17)
    - March 6, 1963: Louisiana, Arkansas, Texas. (Box 17)
    - October 23, 1963: Meridian, Idaho. (Box 17)
    - December 6-7, 1963: APO 253, France. (Box 17)
    - April 17, 1964: Fallon AFS: Nevada. (Box 17)
    - April 26, 1964: Las Vegas, Nevada. (Box 17)
    - April 26, 1964: La Madera, NM. (Box 17)
    - April 28, 1964: Minot AFB, N. Dakota. (Box 17)
    - May 24, 1964: Millinocket, Maine. (Box 17)
    - May 26, 1964: Cambridge, Mass. (Box 17)
    - July 10, 1964: Cape Guardian, MO. Jackson, Miss., Belleville. (Box 17)
    - July 16, 1964: S. Houghton Lake, Mich. (Box 17)
    - July 24, 1954: Langley AFB, Virginia. (Box 17)
    - November 16-24, 1964: 18.10 N. 66.12 W. Atlantic. (Box 17)
    - Ocean November 19, 1964: 34.55 N. 164.05 E. Pacific Ocean. (Box 17)
    - December 4, 1964: Baker, Oregon. (Box 17)
    - December 21, 1964: Harrisonburg, VA. (Box 17)
    - December 29, 1964: Patuxent River, MD. (Box 17)
    - January 23, 1965: Williamsburg, VA. (Box 17)
    - January 24-28, 1965: Alaska. (Box 17)
    - April 4, 1965: Keesler AFB, Mississippi. (Box 17)
    - April 10-14, 1965: Misawa AFB, Japan. (Box 17)
    - June 8 - 9, 1965: Turkey. (Box 17)
    - June 29, 1965:Frankfurt, Germany. (Box 17)
    - July 3, 1965, July 6, 1965: Antarctic & Arlington, TX. (Box 17)
    - July 13, 1965: Penn. and Ohio. (Box 17)
    - July 22, 1965: Forbes AFB, Kansas. (Box 17)
    - July 31-August 3, 1965: Oklahoma. (Box 17)
    - August 1, 1965: Ent AFB, Colo. (Box 17)
    - August 3, 1965: Cocoa, Fla. (Box 17)
    - August 5, 1965: Chicago, IL. (Box 17)
    - August 1-2, 1965: Whiteman AFB, MO. (Box 17)
    - August 20, 1965: Plattsburg, NY. (Box 17)
    - August 28, 1965: Glasgow AFB, Mont. (Box 17)
    - August 30, 1965: Urbana, OH. (Box 17)
    - August 31, 1965: Nevada. (Box 17)
    - September 22, 1965: Clover, Minn. (Box 17)
    - September 25, 1965: Rodeo, NM. (Box 17)
    - September 26, 1965: Licking County, OH. (Box 17)
    - September 27, 1965: Swanlake, NY. (Box 17)
    - October 1965 - June 27, 1966: Anderson AFB, Guam. (Box 17)
    - October 7, 1965: Edwards AFB, CA. (Box 17)
    - October 14, 1965: Sawyer AFB, Mich. (Box 17)
    - March 25, 1966: Truax Field, WI. (Box 17)
    - May 4, 1966: Charleston WV. (Box 17)
    - May 7, 1966: Goodfellow AFB, TX. (Box 17)
    - August 23, 1966: Danang, Vietnam. (Box 17)
    - August 24, 1966: Carpio, ND. (Box 17)
    - September 5, 1966: Finland AFS, Minn. (Box 17)
    - September 6, 1966: Suffolk County AFB, NY. (Box 17)
    - September 9, 1966: Franklin Springs, NY. (Box 17)
    - September 28, 1966: Wilmington, OH. (Box 17)
    - October 26, 1966: Cold Bay, Alaska. (Box 17)
    - November 8, 1966: Saginaw, Minn. (Box 17)
    - December 25, 1966: Monroe, Ore. (Box 17)
    - January 16, 1967: Charleston, SC. (Box 18)
    - February 9, 1967: Odessa, Delaware. (Box 18)
    - February 12, 1967: Grand Rapids, Mich. (Box 18)
    - February 16, 1967: Striughton, Wisc. (Box 18)
    - February 20, 1967: Oxford, Wisc. (Box 18)
    - February 23, 1967: Glasgow AFB, Montana. (Box 18)
    - March 6, 1967: Benton Harbor, Mich. (Box 18)
    - March 9, 1967: Onawa, Iowa. (Box 18)
    - March 22, 1967: Wapello, Iowa. (Box 18)
    - March 24, 1967: Belt, Mont. (Box 18)
    - March 26, 1967: New Winchester, OH. (Box 18)
    - April 10-11, 1967: Houma, LA. (Box 18)
    - July 10, 1967: Lizelia, Mississippi. (Box 18)
    - July 30-31, 1967: Kernville, CA. (Box 18)
    - September 11, 1967: Kincheloe AFB, Mich. (Box 18)
    - October 18, 1967: Lake Charles, LA. (Box 18)
    - February 4, 1968: Redlands, CA. (Box 18)
    - February 9, 1968: Groveton, MO. (Box 18)
    - March 6, 1968: Amarillo, TX. (Box 18)
    - July 11, 1968: Nielson AFB, Alaska. (Box 18)
  - Series III: Research Files, 1904-1969
    - #1: Civilian Saucer Intelligence of New York (CSI) Newsletter. 4/54-9/56 (Box 18)
    - #2: CSI Newsletter. 12/56-11/57 (Box 18)
    - #3: CSI Newsletter. 12/57-7/59 (Box 18)
    - #4: Declassified Project Grudge and Project Blue Book reports. (Box 18)
    - #5: Lists of Combined and Omitted Paged from Blue Book Status .Reports #8-12, and full copies of these reports. (Box 18)
    - #6: "Miscellaneous Notes - Miscellaneous." Preliminary outline of book JEM planned to write rebutting the Condon Report. Material includes "File Index" of subjects; after alphabetized tabs are case notes and references on many of these subjects. (Box 18)
    - #1: Lists of Projects Sign, Grudge, Blue Book sightings,, radar events. 1948-1953 (Box 18)
    - #2: Lists of Project Blue book sightings. 1954-1958 (Box 18)
    - #3: Lists of Project Blue Book sightings - 1966-1969 (Box 18)
    - #4: Lists of Air Force-investigated sightings 24 June 1947 - July 4, 1949Plus over 200 typed case summaries. (Box 18)
    - #5: Project Grudge Analysis by Leon Davidson: on Ball lightning; miscellaneous information. (Box 18)
    - #1: USAF Information, including AF Regulation No. 80-17, GEOREF; Maps; PDO account numbers; AF Bases & Stations, etc. (Box 18)
    - #2: Blue Book cases not reproduced in NICAP edition, but collected by JEM; Project Sign notes; list of significant Grudge cases; Miscellaneous correspondence, etc. (Box 18)
    - #3: Case summaries; typed text of articles; typed text of letters sent elsewhere. (Box 18)
    - #4: Typed case summaries; re-typed articles. (Box 18)
    - #5: "Case Notes." Handwritten and typed notes on various sightings, alphabetized. "Cruttwell Report,"; Papua, New Guinea: Father Gill sighting. March 1960 (Box 18)
    - #1: Miscellaneous articles, newsletters, correspondence. (Box 18)
    - #2: Correspondence from UFO propulsion theorists; visionaries, prophets, pseudoscientists; astrologers. (Box 19)
    - #3: Miscellaneous UFO softcover books: UFO Evidence: UFOs A New Look: Symposium on Unidentified Flying Objects, etc. July 29th, 1968 (Box 19)
    - #4: NICAP Mass. Investigating Subcommittee (Chairman, Ray Fowler). (Box 19)
    - #5: NICAP Mass. Investigating Subcommittee (Chairman, Ray Fowler). (Box 19)
    - #6: Unanswered letters: Pseudo-science; kooks, etc. (Box 19)
    - #7: Condon Report controversy; Colorado U. clips; reprints of JEM talks: Correspondence with U. Thant & AIAA; George Kocher correspondence, sighting reports; Dave H. Rowe correspondence; Dexter-Hillsdale notes, clippings. (Box 19)
    - #8: ITT Research Institute; David Lowe photographs; copies of newsclips; Vandenberg AFB telephone directory, Nov. 1968; microwaves on birds; miscellaneous notes for talks; perpetual calendar; astronomical ephemeris. (Box 19)
    - Computer printout of requested Blue Book Reports. 1904-1967 (Box 19)
  - Series IV: Publications Relating to Project Grudge, Blue Book, Condon, and others. 1951-1969
    - Project Grudge and Blue Book Reports 1-12. 1951-1953 (Box 20)
    - Final Report on the Scientific Study of Unidentified Flying Objects, Dr. E. U. Condon, Director, Volumes 1-3, all annotated by JEM. (Box 20)
    - The UFO Evidence, edited by Richard H. Hall, (annotated by JEM). 1964 (Box 20)
    - Report on the UFO Wave of 1947, Ted Bloecher. 1967 (Box 20)
    - Flying Saucers Analysis of Blue Book Special Report #14, by Leon Davidson. (Box 20)
    - Science and the UFOs, National Amateur Astronomers. 1969 (Box 20)
    - UFOS: a new look, edited by Keyhoe and Lore. 1969 (Box 20)
    - UFOS and related subjects: an annotated bibliography, by Lynn Catoe, Library of Congress. (Box 20)
  - Series V: Photographic Materials.
    - Photos, Films, Slides. (Box 21)
    - Slides for talks, UFOs, Mistaken Objects. (Box 22)
    - 12 UFO carton slides. (Box 22)
    - 15 FEM UFO slides. (Box 22)
    - 17 Contrails of wing of A/C (sun dog?). (Box 22)
    - 18 JEM slides (NICAP) and Grindstone cloud. (Box 22)
    - 19 JEM assistant slides including NASA phots AF photo. (Box 22)
    - 20 Cholderhose photos. White sands craft. Early rocket flights. (Box 22)
    - 21 Unidentified film roll. (Box 22)
    - 22 Negatives of craters. (Box 22)
  - Series VI: Audio-tapes: Interviews of UFO Sightings Witnesses by JEM. 1954-1967
    - Tapes 1-18. (Box 23)
    - Tapes 19-36. (Box 24)
    - Tapes 37-53. (Box 25)
    - Tapes 54-60, A-I. (Box 26)
    - Tapes K-V. (Box 27)
    - Tapes 1-9, A-H. (Box 28)
    - Tapes 1-13. (Box 29)
    - Tapes 14-20. (Box 30)
  - Series VII: Supplemental Materials. 1960-1971
    - LP Record (33 1/3) record: CBC Radio-Canada, Documentary series on UFOs. (Box 31)
    - Sony Tape Recorder/Case (for use on reel-to-reel tapes). (Box 31)
    - Two (2) samples of scorched earth from reported UFO landing site, South Hill, Virginia, 4/21/67. Also one control sample. (Box 31)
    - White Looseleaf Notebook: Lists of tapes, transcriptions; contents of hard cover notebooks, large books, brown file boxes; inventory of photos. (Box 31)
    - Miscellaneous files. 1960-1962 (Box 32)
      Box 32 contents: files related to Titan Missiles, including The Committee Against Ringing Tucson with Titans. Includes correspondence, minutes, articles, and printed materials relating to McDonald's activities to protest the placement of intercontinental ballistic missile base in the Tucson area.
    - Miscellaneous files. 1970-1971 (Box 33)
      Box 33 contents: files relating to the debate on the environmental effects of supersonic transports, includes his statement before the House Subcommittee on Transportation Appropriations concerning the transport program.
- Subgroup 2: General Research Files, 1953-1997
  - Series I: Research Files, 1953-1997
    - Absorption Data - water and ice. (Box 34)
    - Absorption of solar radiation by water vapor. (Box 34)
    - Acoustics. (Box 34)
    - Aerodynamics. (Box 34)
    - Air pollution. (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - pre 1950 clippings. (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - Arizona (2 folders). (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - Arizona - Tucson Daily Citizen. (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - Pima County. 1969 (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - Phoenix and non-Tucson Arizona. (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - Tucson. (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - mining. (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - sulfur dioxide. (Box 34)
    - Air pollution - Los Angeles and other California. (Box 34)
    - Aircraft performance and effects on atmos.. (Box 34)
    - Aircraft - airport sequenced approach lights. (Box 34)
    - Aircraft - cabin depressurization effect. (Box 34)
    - Aircraft - Jettisoning of fuel. (Box 34)
    - Aircraft - shock waves on wings. (Box 34)
    - Airglow - astronomy. (Box 34)
    - Arctic. (Box 34)
    - Arid land - colloquium climatology. (Box 34)
    - Arid land - Rockefeller. (Box 34)
    - Arid zone climatology. (Box 34)
    - Astronomy. (Box 34)
    - Selected astronomical data. (Box 34)
    - Aurora. September 22-23 1957 (Box 34)
    - Balloon, near flight records. (Box 34)
    - Balloon dynamics. (Box 34)
    - Balloon inflation back-pressures. (Box 34)
    - Banner clouds. (Box 35)
    - Biology, cellular. (Box 35)
    - Bomb phenomena. (Box 35)
    - Bomb phenomena - other than fallout. (Box 35)
    - Brown Mountain Lights. (Box 35)
    - Brownian movement - history. (Box 35)
    - Calendar. (Box 35)
    - Carbon 14 and Carbon Dioxide. (Box 35)
    - Carbon monoxide. (Box 35)
    - Chemistry and composition of the atmosphere. (Box 35)
    - CAT - Clear Air Turbulence. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - general. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - pre 1950 clippings. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Pleistocene Age. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Pleistocene. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Paleoclimatology. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Paleoclimatology pre 1950 clippings. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Homogeneity of Records. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona cloud cover study. 1957-1958 (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona Arizona seasonal precip. Data. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona diurnal variation of precip. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona precip. double mass study. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona precip. correlation studies. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona precip. length of record study. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona precip. 10 year moving averages. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona winter precip. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona precip frequency distribution of amounts. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona precip tetrachoric correlation test. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona diurnal variation of mixing ratio. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona mountain precip. storage. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona precipitable water. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Arizona winter wind directions. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - data Mexico. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - data precipitation deck notes. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - data analysis effects of inhemogeniety. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - desert precipitation rates. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Southwest secular precip. trends. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Southwest secular precip. trends. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - Western U.S. precip - 10 year moving ave. (Box 35)
    - Climatology - U.S. mean mixing ratios (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. rel. humidity - time x-sections. (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. monthly mean relative humidity. (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. mean precipitable water distrib. (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. temp. precip. relations, wettest vs. driest. (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. precip. seasonal and annual variability. (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. precipitation efficiency. (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. - mixing ratio - cross-section of Southern U.S. (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. precipitable water. (Box 36)
    - Climatology - U.S. upper level anticyclone. (Box 36)
    - Climatic models. (Box 36)
    - Climate modification. (Box 36)
    - Climate modification inadvertent (2 folders). (Box 36)
    - Climate modification inadvertent, La Porte Anom. (Box 36)
    - Cloud condensation level local observ. (Box 36)
    - Cloud modification rainmaking pre 1950s clippings. (Box 36)
    - Cloud photogrametry K-17, misc. notes. (Box 36)
    - Cloud photogrametry K-17 IBM data. (Box 36)
    - Cloud photogrametry K-17 calibration. (Box 36)
    - Cloud physics, general. (Box 36)
    - Cloud photographs, pre 1950's clippings. (Box 36)
    - Cloud photographs. (Box 36)
    - Cloud physics 1961 Australian Conference. 1961 (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding - misc. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding reports - misc. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding Arizona. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding Arizona - Flagstaff. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding Australian experiments. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding benefit/cost ratio. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding - California Kern County. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding Quakers - Bosco. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding Jeffery. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding Quakery - Krick. (Box 36)
    - Cloud seeding carbon black (2 folders). (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding dry ice. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding and ecology. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding evolution and statistics. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding - fringe cases and quakery. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding - Elliott North American Weather Cons. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding frontal storms. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding India. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding legal problems. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding legislation. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding in Mexico. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding Oregon. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding Owyhee Project. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding people problems. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding silver iodide. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding AgI cost analysis. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding by water drops. (Box 37)
    - Cloud seeding summer 1957. (Box 37)
    - Coalescenece. (Box 37)
    - Coalesence - droplet growth in clouds. (Box 37)
    - Coalescance vs. freezing. (Box 37)
    - Coalescance project with Wisconsin. 1953-54 (Box 37)
    - Collection Theory. (Box 37)
    - Collection Theory Brownian Movement. (Box 37)
    - Collision Theory. (Box 37)
    - Collision Theory Foote. (Box 37)
    - Drop growth by condensation and collection. (Box 37)
    - Collision Theory growth of snowflakes by Wake Capture. (Box 37)
    - Combustion and flames. (Box 37)
    - Combustion process. (Box 37)
    - Comets. (Box 37)
    - Composition and evolution of earth's atmosphere - Berkner and Marshall. (Box 38)
    - Computers. (Box 38)
    - Computers pre 1950 clippings. (Box 38)
    - Condensation level, study of lifting. (Box 38)
    - Condensation nucleation Twomey. (Box 38)
    - Condensation nucleation. (Box 38)
    - Condensation nucleation homogeneous. (Box 38)
    - Condensation nuclei condensation on Ions. (Box 38)
    - Condensation nucleation on insoluble particles. (Box 38)
    - Condensation nuclei observation and measurement. (Box 38)
    - Condensation due to dynamic effects. (Box 38)
    - Condensation criterion. (Box 38)
    - Condensation criterion. (Box 38)
    - Convection. (Box 38)
    - Convection - numerical modeling. (Box 38)
    - Convection modeling. (Box 38)
    - Valves of constants. (Box 38)
    - Contrails. (Box 38)
    - Conolis effect. (Box 38)
    - Coronas and St. Elmos fire. (Box 38)
    - Cosmic rays. (Box 38)
    - Cosmic rays Chapman Effect. (Box 38)
    - Crystallography metals. (Box 38)
    - Cube roots, calculation of. (Box 38)
    - Cumulus clouds. (Box 38)
    - Cumulus clouds squires reprints. (Box 38)
    - Cumulus clouds caused by fires. (Box 38)
    - Deliquescence and hydrates. (Box 38)
    - Deposition paper. (Box 38)
    - Desalination. (Box 38)
    - Desert. (Box 38)
    - Dew. (Box 38)
    - Diffusion. (Box 38)
    - Diffusion Caesar's Breath. (Box 38)
    - Diffusion, atmospheric long range transport. (Box 38)
    - Diffusion coefficient - compensated. (Box 38)
    - Diffusional growth of drops - steady-state approximation. (Box 38)
    - Diffusional growth of drops in an updraft. (Box 38)
    - Diffusional growth of drops - Langmuir. (Box 38)
    - Diffusional growth of particles. (Box 38)
    - Diffusional growth of ice droplets. (Box 38)
    - Diffusional growth of ice crystals. (Box 38)
    - Distribution functions. (Box 38)
    - Drag - parachutes - dynamics. (Box 38)
    - Drop breakup. (Box 38)
    - Drop physics. (Box 38)
    - Drop production by artificial means (Box 38)
    - Drop shape. (Box 38)
    - Drop size distributions covering fraction theory. (Box 39)
    - Drop size measurements spattering. (Box 39)
    - Drop size distribution measurement of. (Box 39)
    - Droplets, very small diam <2m.. (Box 39)
    - Droughts. (Box 39)
    - Dust devils. (Box 39)
    - Dust and dust nuclei. (Box 39)
    - Dust - stratospheric. (Box 39)
    - Dynamics of cumulus clouds bubble spectra K17. (Box 39)
    - Dynamics of cumulus clouds. (Box 39)
    - Dynamics - drag flow past a cylinder. (Box 39)
    - Dynamics - drag flow past spheres. (Box 39)
    - Earthquakes and earth interior. (Box 39)
    - Ecology (2 folders). (Box 39)
    - Ecology, food and population problems. (Box 39)
    - Ecology - pesticides. (Box 39)
    - Electricity of the atmosphere. (Box 39)
    - Electrostactics of drops and clouds. (Box 39)
    - Electrostatics of clouds and drops - Latham. (Box 39)
    - Empiricism. (Box 39)
    - Energetics. (Box 39)
    - Energy - vertical distribution of internal and potential. (Box 39)
    - Evaporation - lakes, etc. (Box 39)
    - Evaporation kinetic model. (Box 39)
    - Evaporation of raindrops - Cholley paper. (Box 39)
    - Evaporation - precipitation fallacy. (Box 39)
    - Evaporation - precipitation ratio. (Box 39)
    - Evolution. (Box 39)
    - Explosion physics. (Box 39)
    - Fall velocity of drops and snow crystals. (Box 39)
    - Fall velocity of spheres. (Box 39)
    - Fall velocity of small particles. (Box 39)
    - Fall velocity of small particles - Facy Effect. (Box 39)
    - Fallout Met. (Box 39)
    - Filters, Millipore. (Box 39)
    - Fire. (Box 39)
    - Fog. (Box 40)
    - Fog dispersal pre 1950 clippings. (Box 40)
    - Fog - ice fog. (Box 40)
    - Fog, numerical modeling of fog. (Box 40)
    - Fog, steam. (Box 40)
    - Fog - drip; collection of fog droplets by plants. (Box 40)
    - Forecasting weather pre 1950's clippings. (Box 40)
    - Free fall parachutes. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nucleation (2 folders). (Box 40)
    - Freezing nucleation homogeneous - thermodynam. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nucleation Fletcher. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nucleation in the atmosphere. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nucleation supercooling. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nucleation due to expansion - pop bottle exp. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nucleation by silver idodide. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nuclei Arizona observations. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nuclei NCAR counter. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nuclei Bowen's Hypothesis. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nuclei from smelter stacks. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nuclei counts. 1958 (Box 40)
    - Freezing nuclei, natural observations and measurements. (Box 40)
    - Freezing nuclei measurements. (Box 40)
    - Friction. (Box 40)
    - Game Theory, etc. (Box 40)
    - Geochronology. (Box 40)
    - Geomagnetism. (Box 40)
    - Green flash. (Box 40)
    - Hail. (Box 40)
    - Hail damage. (Box 40)
    - Heat budget of atmosphere latent heat transport. (Box 40)
    - Helium. (Box 40)
    - History of cloud physics. (Box 40)
    - History of cloud physics Bergeron Hypothesis. (Box 41)
    - History of cloud physics - James Espy. (Box 41)
    - History of cloud modification. (Box 41)
    - History of diffusional growth of cloud droplets. (Box 41)
    - History of rainmaking (2 folders). (Box 41)
    - Hornet light. (Box 41)
    - Humidity measurement psychrometry. (Box 41)